We’ve all heard cats meow and hiss, but why do they purr?
我们都听过猫咪喵喵叫和发出嘶嘶声，但它们为什么会打呼噜呢？
There are a number of theories out there - from the commonly held belief that they are simply happy, to British comedian Eddie Izzard’s light-hearted suggestion that they are impersonating a drill.
关于这个问题有不少说法——普遍观点认为猫咪只是因为开心才打呼噜，而英国喜剧演员埃迪·伊扎德还曾开玩笑说，猫咪打呼噜是在模仿电钻的声音。
While they do purr when tickled or caressed to show their appreciation for attention, cats also make the noise when not in our company.
猫咪在被胳肢或爱抚时，确实会通过打呼噜来表达对这份关注的喜悦，但即便身边没人，它们也会发出这种声音。
The purring noise is a consistent pulsing sound that occurs while they both inhale and exhale breath.
呼噜是一种持续的脉冲声，无论吸气还是呼气时都会产生。
The word ‘purr’ is a great example of onomatopoeia and refers to the constant noise which ranges in frequency between 25 and 150 hertz.
“呼噜”这个词是拟声词的绝佳范例，指的是这种频率在25到150赫兹之间的持续声响。
For a long time, scientists debated how cats purred.
长期以来，科学家们一直在争论猫咪打呼噜的原理。
Most people believe that the cat’s brain signals the laryngeal muscles to vibrate and function like a valve, opening and closing the space between the vocal cords.
大多数人认为，猫咪的大脑会向喉部肌肉发送信号，使其产生振动，就像阀门一样开合声带之间的空隙。
What triggers this reaction is debated.
至于触发这种反应的原因，目前仍存有争议。
Some argue that the cat intends to purr, while others say it may be due to endorphins released by the brain as a reaction to pleasure, or pain.
有人认为猫咪是有意为之，也有人表示，这可能是大脑在愉悦或疼痛时释放内啡肽所引发的反应。
According to Leslie A. Lyons, an assistant professor at the School of Veterinary Medicine at the University of California, cats often purr while stressed, such as when they head to the vets or are recovering from an injury.
加州大学兽医学院助理教授莱斯利·A·莱昂斯表示，猫咪在感到压力时也常会打呼噜，比如去看兽医或者受伤恢复期间。
So what are the potential benefits of this ‘drilling’ sound?
那么这种类似“电钻”的声音有什么潜在益处呢？
Some scientists believe the vibrations that ripple through the cats’ bodies may actually promote muscle development, heal bones and injuries, ease breathing and lessen pain.
一些科学家认为，在猫咪体内扩散的振动，实际上有助于促进肌肉发育、修复骨骼和伤口、缓解呼吸不畅并减轻疼痛。
It could even help to soothe discomfort in a similar way to a child sucking their thumb.
这种振动甚至能像孩子吮吸拇指那样，帮助猫咪缓解不适感。
So, the purring of a cat may have more uses than just telling you they’re enjoying attention.
由此可见，猫咪打呼噜的作用远不止告诉你它们很享受你的关注。
It’s also important to remember that not all cats can purr.
还有一点需要注意，并非所有猫科动物都会打呼噜。
Some bigger felines, like lions, can’t, and only roar.
一些体型较大的猫科动物，比如狮子，就只会吼叫不会打呼噜。
So, the next time you hear a roar, it probably isn’t your pussy cat, and you might need to run.
所以下次如果你听到吼叫声，那大概率不会是你家的小猫咪，而你可能得赶紧跑了。